Teacher: Hello? Hello? Can you hear me?
Micaela: (Hi, yes, fine. I can hear you.)
Teacher: Sorry? You’re on mute.
Micaela: Is it OK now?
Teacher: Yes, fine now!
Hello, I’m Harry, from English House Language School.
Micaela: Hi, Harry.
Teacher: Hi there. OK, can I check your details first?
Micaela: Yes, of course.
Teacher: What’s your first name?
Micaela: Micaela.
Teacher: How do you spell it?
Micaela: M-I-C-A-E-L-A.
Teacher: M-I-C-A-E-L-A
– is that right?
Micaela: Yes, that’s right.
Teacher: And … what’s your surname?
Micaela Vazquez.
Teacher: Vazquez. Is that V-A-S…?
Micaela: No, it’s V-A-Z-Q-U-E-Z.
Teacher: V-A-Z-Q-U-E-Z.
OK. Er How old are you, Micaela?
Micaela: I’m 25.
Teacher: Where are you from?
Micaela: I’m from Argentina.
Teacher: Where in Argentina?
Micaela: From Buenos Aires.
Teacher: What’s your address?
Micaela: It’s Florida one six five.
Teacher: Florida’s the street name? Number one six five?
Micaela: Yes.
Teacher: What’s your postcode?
Micaela: Sorry?
Teacher: You know, the postcode.
Micaela: Ah yes. It’s C- one zero zero five A-A-C.
Teacher: C- one zero zero five A-A-C.
Great. What’s your email address?
Micaela: It’s m dot vazquez at mail dot com.
Teacher: And what’s your phone number?
Micaela: My mobile or my home phone,
my landline?
Teacher: Both – mobile and landline.
Micaela: My mobile is plus five four – that’s for Argentina – then one one, one five,
eight nine three four, five five six eight.
Teacher: Plus five four, one one, one five, eight nine three four, five five six eight.
Great. And your landline?
Micaela: Plus five four, one one, six zero two three, five four four two.
Teacher: Plus five four, one one, six zero two three, five four four two.
Micaela: That’s right.
Teacher: OK, that’s great. So, what do you do, Micaela?
Micaela: I’m at university. I’m a medical student…